<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MiwokTabbed</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->

    <!--Universal studios-->
    <string name="universal_about">
        Universal Studios Hollywood is a film studio and theme park in the Universal City county island (unincorporated) area of the San Fernando Valley of Los Angeles County, California, United States. It is one of the oldest and most famous Hollywood film studios still in use. Its official marketing headline is "The Entertainment Capital of LA". It was initially created to offer tours of the real Universal Studios sets and is the first of many full-fledged Universal Studios Theme Parks located across the world.
    </string>
    <string name="universal_name">Universal Studios, Hollywood</string>
    <string name="univeral_address">100 Universal City Plaza, Universal City, CA 91608</string>
    <string name="universal_contact">Phone: (800) 864-8377</string>
    <string name="universal_lat">34.1381168</string>
    <string name="universal_lng">-118.35337830000003</string>

    <!--Gryffith obersvatory-->
    <string name="gryff_about">
        Griffith Observatory is a facility in Los Angeles, California, sitting on the south-facing slope of Mount Hollywood in Los Angeles Griffith Park. It commands a view of the Los Angeles Basin, including Downtown Los Angeles to the southeast, Hollywood to the south, and the Pacific Ocean to the southwest. The observatory is a popular tourist attraction with an excellent view of the Hollywood Sign and an extensive array of space and science-related displays. Admission has been free since the observatory\'s opening in 1935, in accordance with the will of Griffith J. Griffith, the benefactor after whom the observatory is named
    </string>
    <string name="gryff_name">Griffith Observatory</string>
    <string name="gryff_address">2800 E Observatory Rd, Los Angeles, CA 90027</string>
    <string name="gryff_contact">Phone: (213) 473 0800</string>
    <string name="gryff_lat">34.11834</string>
    <string name="gryff_lng">-118.30034</string>

    <!--Santa Moica Pier-->
    <string name="sm_pier_about">
        The Santa Monica Pier is a large double-jointed pier at the foot of Colorado Avenue in Santa Monica, California. With an iconic entrance, the pier is popular with residents and visitors as a landmark that is over 100 years old.
    </string>
    <string name="sm_pier_name">Santa Monica Pier</string>
    <string name="sm_pier_address">200 Santa Monica Pier A, Santa Monica, CA 90401</string>
    <string name="sm_pier_contact">Phone: (310) 458-8900</string>
    <string name="sm_pier_lat">34.0093061</string>
    <string name="sm_pier_lng">-118.5000063</string>

    <!--Disneyland-->
    <string name="disney_land_about">
            Disneyland Park, originally Disneyland, is the first of two theme parks built at the Disneyland Resort in Anaheim, California, opened on July 17, 1955. It is the only theme park designed and built under the direct supervision of Walt Disney. It was originally the only attraction on the property; its official name was changed to Disneyland Park to distinguish it from the expanding complex in the 1990s
    </string>
    <string name="disney_land_name">Disneyland Park</string>
    <string name="disney_land_address">1313 Disneyland Dr, Anaheim, CA 92802</string>
    <string name="disney_land_contact">Phone: (714) 781-4636</string>
    <string name="disney_land_lat">33.8120962</string>
    <string name="disney_land_lng">-117.9211629</string>

    <!--Getty Villa-->
    <string name="getty_about">
            The Getty Villa is one of two locations of the J. Paul Getty Museum. Located at the easterly end of the Malibu coast in the Pacific Palisades neighborhood of Los Angeles, California, USA,[2] the Getty Villa is an educational center and museum dedicated to the study of the arts and cultures of ancient Greece, Rome, and Etruria. The collection has 44,000 Greek, Roman, and Etruscan antiquities dating from 6,500 BC to 400 AD, including the Lansdowne Heracles and the Victorious Youth. The UCLA/Getty Master’s Program in Archaeological and Ethnographic Conservation is housed on this campus. The collection is documented and presented through the online GettyGuide as well as through audio tours.
    </string>
    <string name="getty_name">Getty Villa</string>
    <string name="getty_address">17985 Pacific Coast Highway, Pacific Palisades, California 90272</string>
    <string name="getty_contact">Phone: (310) 440-7300</string>
    <string name="getty_lat">34.0458857</string>
    <string name="getty_lng">-118.5648608</string>

    <!--The Natural History Museum-->
    <string name="nh_museum_about">
            The Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County (abbreviated NHM) is the largest natural and historical museum in the western United States, Its collections include nearly 35 million specimens and artifacts and cover 4.5 billion years of history. This large collection is comprised not only of specimens for exhibition, but also of vast research collections housed on and offsite.
    </string>
    <string name="nh_museum_name">Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County</string>
    <string name="nh_museum_address">900 W Exposition Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90007</string>
    <string name="nh_museum_contact">Phone: (213) 763-3466</string>
    <string name="nh_museum_lat">34.0169567</string>
    <string name="nh_museum_lng">-118.2887703</string>

    <!--Los Angeles County Museum of Art-->
    <string name="lacma_about">
            The Los Angeles County Museum of Art is an art museum located on Wilshire Boulevard in the Miracle Mile vicinity of Los Angeles. LACMA is on Museum Row, adjacent to the La Brea Tar Pits. LACMA is the largest art museum in the western United States.
    </string>
    <string name="lacma_name">The Los Angeles County Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="lacma_address">5905 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036</string>
    <string name="lacma_contact">Phone: (323) 857 6000</string>
    <string name="lacma_lat">34.0639323</string>
    <string name="lacma_lng">-118.3592293</string>

    <!--La_brea_tarpits-->
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_about">
            The La Brea Tar Pits are a group of tar pits around which Hancock Park was formed in urban Los Angeles. Natural asphalt has seeped up from the ground in this area for tens of thousands of years. The tar is often covered with dust, leaves, or water.
    </string>
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_name">Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County</string>
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_address">5801 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036</string>
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_contact">Phone: (213) 763-3499</string>
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_lat">34.0638079</string>
    <string name="la_brea_tarpits_lng">-118.3554338</string>

    <!--Peterson automative museum-->
    <string name="peterson_auto_about">
            The Petersen Automotive Museum is located on Wilshire Boulevard along Museum Row in the Miracle Mile neighborhood of Los Angeles. One of the world\'s largest automotive museums, the Petersen Automotive Museum is a nonprofit organization specializing in automobile history and related educational programs.
    </string>
    <string name="peterson_auto_name">Petersen Automotive Museum</string>
    <string name="peterson_auto_address">6060 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036</string>
    <string name="peterson_auto_contact">Phone:(323) 930-2277</string>
    <string name="peterson_auto_lat">34.062348</string>
    <string name="peterson_auto_lng">-118.3611336</string>

    <!--Museum of Tolerance-->
    <string name="museum_tolerance_about">
            The Museum of Tolerance, a multimedia museum in Los Angeles, California, United States, is designed to examine racism and prejudice around the world with a strong focus on the history of the Holocaust.
    </string>
    <string name="museum_tolerance_name">Museum of Tolerance  </string>
    <string name="museum_tolerance_address">9786 W Pico Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90035</string>
    <string name="museum_tolerance_contact">Phone:(310) 772-2505</string>
    <string name="museum_tolerance_lat">34.053698</string>
    <string name="museum_tolerance_lng">-118.4016724</string>

    <!--California Science Center-->
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_about">
            The California Science Center is a state agency and museum located in Exposition Park, Los Angeles, next to the Natural History Museum of Los Angeles County and the University of Southern California.
    </string>
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_name">California Science Center</string>
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_address">700 Exposition Park Dr, Los Angeles, CA 90037</string>
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_contact">Phone: (323) 724-3623</string>
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_lat">34.0158653</string>
    <string name="ca_science_ctr_lng">-118.2861082</string>


    <!--Leo Carrillo State Park-->
    <string name="leo_c">
            Leo Carrillo State Park offers swimming, surfing, windsurfing, surf fishing, and beachcombing. Beachgoers can explore tide pools, sea caves, and reefs. Away from shore there is a shady campground and backcountry hiking trails.
    </string>
    <string name="leo_c_name">Leo Carrillo State Park</string>
    <string name="leo_c_address">35000 W Pacific Coast Highway, Malibu, CA 90265</string>
    <string name="leo_c_contact">Phone: (310) 457-8143</string>
    <string name="leo_c_lat">34.044444</string>
    <string name="leo_c_lng">-118.933889</string>

    <!--Muscle Beach -->
    <string name="muscle_beach">
            Muscle Beach refers to the exclusive Santa Monica location of the birthplace of the physical fitness boom in the US during the 20th century, started in 1934 with predominantly gymnastics activities on the south side of the Santa Monica Pier.
    </string>
    <string name="muscle_beach_name">Muscle Beach</string>
    <string name="muscle_beach_address">1800 Ocean Front Walk, Venice, CA 9029</string>
    <string name="muscle_beach_contact">Phone: (310) 399-2775</string>
    <string name="muscle_beach_lat">33.9854323</string>
    <string name="muscle_beach_lng">-118.4727025</string>

    <!--Dockweiler Beach -->
    <string name="dockweiler_beach">
    Dockweiler State Beach is a beach in Los Angeles, California, with 3.75 miles of shoreline and a hang gliding practice and training area.    </string>
    <string name="dockweiler_beach_name">Dockweiler State Beach </string>
    <string name="dockweiler_beach_address">12001 Vista Del Mar, Playa Del Rey, CA 90293</string>
    <string name="dockweiler_beach_contact">Phone: (424) 526-7777</string>
    <string name="dockweiler_beach_lat">33.9308251</string>
    <string name="dockweiler_beach_lng">-118.5051035</string>


    <!--Venice beach -->
    <string name="venice_beach">
    This well-known, beachfront destination is home to an array of street performers and funky shops.    </string>
    <string name="venice_beach_name">Venice Beach </string>
    <string name="venice_beach_address">Venice Fishing Pier, Venice, CA 90292</string>
    <string name="venice_beach_contact">Phone: (310) 396-6794</string>
    <string name="venice_beach_lat">33.9782453</string>
    <string name="venice_beach_lng">-118.5366945</string>

    <!--Marina beach -->
    <string name="marina_beach">
    Playground, picnic tables and other kid-friendly attractions at a surf-free sheltered beach.    </string>
    <string name="marina_beach_name">Marina Beach (Mother\'s Beach)</string>
    <string name="marina_beach_address">4135 Admiralty Way, Marina Del Rey, CA 90292</string>
    <string name="marina_beach_contact">Phone: (424) 526-7777</string>
    <string name="marina_beach_lat">33.9815937</string>
    <string name="marina_beach_lng">-118.5281543</string>

    <!--Will Rogers State Beach -->
    <string name="will_rogers_beach">
    Will Rogers State Beach is a beach park on the Santa Monica Bay, at the Pacific coast of Southern California </string>
    <string name="will_rogers_beach_name">Will Rogers State Beach</string>
    <string name="will_rogers_beach_address">17000 Pacific Coast Hwy, Pacific Palisades, CA 90272</string>
    <string name="will_rogers_beach_contact">Phone: (424) 526-7777</string>
    <string name="will_rogers_beach_lat">34.0375209</string>
    <string name="will_rogers_beach_lng">-118.6117521</string>

</resources>


